dawnsign.com 2010-06-25

# DawnSign Press.com Privacy Policy

* **Privacy Notice**
* Conditions Of Use
| 

## **The following policy applies to the DAWNSIGN.COM site.**

DAWNSIGN.COM is committed to protecting the privacy and security of its online visitors. This policy statement provides our visitors with an overview of the measures we have taken to provide a safe online environment. **By visiting DAWNSIGN.COM, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.**

## **Personally Identifiable Information**

We only collect personally identifiable information from our visitors when our visitors voluntarily submit such information. We consider the following, among other things, to be personally identifiable information: first and last name, email address, street address, and phone number. We may request personally identifiable information in connection with contests, surveys, content submissions, requests for suggestions, and site registration.

##  **For Individuals**

In some areas of our site, we collect personally identifiable information from individuals. We use that information to customize the content on DAWNSIGN.COM for individuals' current and future needs. We also use this personally identifiable information to provide individuals, via email or other means, information about materials, activities, or other things that may be of interest. However, individuals always have the opportunity to unsubscribe from communication via email if they choose to do so.

##  **For Teachers**

When teachers register at our site, we use their sign-in information, which contains personally identifiable information, to ensure that the teacher has access to certain areas of the site. We also use personally identifiable information that teachers provide to us to customize the content on DAWNSIGN.COM for teachers' current and future needs. In addition, we use this personally identifiable information to provide teachers, via email or other means, information about materials, activities, or other things that may be of interest. However, teachers always have the opportunity to unsubscribe from communication via email if they choose to do so.

##  **Non-Personally Identifiable Information and the Use of Cookie Technology**

We collect non-personally identifiable information through the use of a software technology called "cookies" and through our visitors' voluntary submissions to us and/or upon our request. By non-personally identifiable information, we are referring to information about our visitors' browsers (e.g. Netscape Navigator or Internet Explorer), operating systems (e.g. Windows or MacIntosh), Internet Service Providers (e.g. AOL or Net.com), and other similar information that we track in aggregate form. The non-personally identifiable information that we track is anonymous and will never be identified with or lead us back to any of our visitors. 

Cookie technology helps us to know how many people visit our site and where visitors go within our site. Cookies are small bits of information we send to your computer. Among other things, this non-personally identifiable information allows us to know which areas are favorites, which areas need improvement, or what technologies and internet services are being used by our visitors so that we may continually improve our visitors' online experience. 

## **Security**

DAWNSIGN.COM ensures that all personally and non-personally identifiable information that it receives via the internet is secure against unauthorized access. This information is kept in a secure system isolated from direct connection to the Internet. This means that no one except DawnSignPress will ever see the information that our visitors send to us, unless we indicate otherwise.

Within the e-commerce portion of our site, individuals and teachers are able to purchase items with the use of a credit card. In such instances, DAWNSIGN.COM uses secure server software over a Secure Socket Layer (SSL) line, the latest technology to protect your credit card information. SSL is the industry standard and among the best software available today for secure commerce transactions. It encrypts all of your credit card information so that the information from your credit card cannot be read as it travels over the internet.

##  **Links to Other Sites**

Visitors will find links from DAWNSIGN.COM to independently owned, controlled, and/or managed World-Wide Web or internet sites whose content we have found of possible interest to our visitors. In many cases, but not always, the links represent cooperative projects or mutual links established with the organizations connected with these sites. While we initially visit sites to which we directly link, please note that we do not monitor or control the content that appears on these sites and such content may be constantly changing. We recommend that children check with their parents or teachers before linking to any new sites and we encourage all end users of DAWNSIGN.COM to read the privacy policies of all linked sites before navigating through them.

##  **Please Note**

We may revise our above policy as the content on our site continues to change.

DAWNSIGN.COM is owned and operated by DawnSignPress, 6130 Nancy Ridge Drive, San Diego, CA 92121-3223. We can be reached by telephone or TTY at 800-549-5350 or by email at [info@dawnsign.com](mailto:info@dawnsign.com). If you have any questions about our privacy policy or practices, or you wish to amend, update, or verify your personal information, or notify us that you want your information deleted from our files, please contact us.
